<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home of Dennis Vesterlund</title><link>https://www.vestern.se/</link><description>Recent content on Home of Dennis Vesterlund</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:50:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.vestern.se/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NextCloud rescue admin permissions</title><link>https://www.vestern.se/posts/homelab/nextcloud_rescue_admin_permissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:50:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.vestern.se/posts/homelab/nextcloud_rescue_admin_permissions/</guid><description>While migrating my local users to oidc I accidentally removed admin privileges on the built-in admin user&amp;hellip; This made continuing the migration difficult since i was unable to access the admin features of NextCloud. Here&amp;rsquo;s a short description of how I rescued my privileges.
To give your user admin privileges you have to edit the NextCloud database. If you are running the NextCloud AIO you can access the database using the following command.</description></item><item><title>Migrate NextCloud AIO data directory</title><link>https://www.vestern.se/posts/homelab/nextcloud_migrate_aio_datadir/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:03:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.vestern.se/posts/homelab/nextcloud_migrate_aio_datadir/</guid><description>When I faced the issue of migrating the storage directory for my AIO NextCloud the official README sent me to a github discussion whit a somewhat vague answer on how to perform the migration. I thought i would document the process for future reference and if this helps someone else perform a migration like this, that&amp;rsquo;s a nice bonus.
Pre migration tasks Before performing any big changes like this you should backup everything.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://www.vestern.se/posts/introduction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 21:30:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.vestern.se/posts/introduction/</guid><description>Hello and welcome to my new site. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that it is time to unifi all my things somewhere and this seems like a nice place to do it.</description></item></channel></rss>